<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Rosaline Xiao - Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Rosaline Xiao - Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 18:28:22 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rosalinexiao.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Limera</title>
      <link>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/id/limera/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 23:02:54 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/id/limera/</guid>
      <description>LIMERA: Professional camera for easy storage LIMERA is a portable camera that proposes a new method of camera storage without compromising professionalty, It implements a swivel body that allows the camera to be transformed into a smaller cylinder which is much easier to store in bags and carry around.
Professional cameras are big, bulky and have a weird shape, whereas LIMERA cuts the bulk of raditional cameres.The project originates from my hoby ofphotography, where l find traditional cameras hard to fit in my back pack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SpaceCube</title>
      <link>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/id/spacecube/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 23:13:24 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/id/spacecube/</guid>
      <description>Ferrofluid Loudspeakers SPACE CUBE is a futuristic loudspeaker that has built-in audio visualization. It features ferrofluid, which dances and changes shape in rhythm with the music that is being played. The loudspeaker has an elegant and futuristic design.
The idea comes from one of my school projects where we discuss and experiment with different materials. Ferrofluid is a special liquid as it is magnetic,so its unique magnetic properties can be used to achieve stunning effects in designing a product.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BENTO&#43;</title>
      <link>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/id/bento/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 23:45:46 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/id/bento/</guid>
      <description>BENTO+: Tableware designed for office workers BENTO+ is a set of specilly designed bento boxes that have a redesigned user experience. It incorporates special hinges that allows the bento boxes to swivel, making it easy to load up with your favorite recipes and lit up to go without having to close each of the bento boxes.
The idea comes from my own experience of bringing breakfast in lunch boxes every day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EzPorter</title>
      <link>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/id/ezporter/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 23:44:46 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/id/ezporter/</guid>
      <description>EzPorter: Fast deployable floating bridge design for rescue EzPorter is portable and fast-deployable bridge system that can be used during foods. It implements diferent modules that can be utilited in diferent combinations to meet different use cases. It can also function as road barriers when not in use.
The idea of EzPorter comes from my own experience in floods. My home town is prone to big food in the summer, and I have experenced being stranded and not able to move due to floods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PLANT COMPANION</title>
      <link>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/ux/plantcompanion/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 20:56:42 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/ux/plantcompanion/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In 2021, there were approximately 973 thousand males and 561 thousand females aged 16 to 44 living alone in the United Kingdom[1]. They crave love and emotional support. As a way to solve the loneliness problem, many young people living alone are eager to keep pets to accompany them, but they cannot due to various reasons. Many of them then choose to keep plants and regard plants as living companions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Logger</title>
      <link>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/id/logger/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 22:44:05 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/id/logger/</guid>
      <description>LOGGER: Contribute to meteorological studies while hiking LOGGER is a smart water bottle that has multiple in-built sensors for environmental measurements. Hikers are able to contribute to scientific research by trekking to remote areas that lack internet connection and weather monitoring. The sensors will collect data while hikers are trekking, and upload the data once it connects to the internet. This allows scientist to collect data first-hand from hikers, data gathered from some of the most unstudied and remote places on Earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DRT Bus Experience Design for Tourists</title>
      <link>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/ux/drt-bus-experience-design-for-tourists/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 22:36:45 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/ux/drt-bus-experience-design-for-tourists/</guid>
      <description>Introduction UN Goal background
The goal for this project is UN Goal No.11
SUSTAINABLE CITIES AND COMMUNITIES
The goal target is:
By 2030, provide access to safe, affordable, accessible and sustainable transport systems for all, improving road safety, notably by expanding public transport.
To achieve these goals, we decided to improve the bus ride experience by designing with buses in public transport. We wanted to provide a more convenient ride for passengers, and we found that tourists, as a group unfamiliar with the local environment, prefer to travel by taxi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design Research on Laundry Habits in Loughborough</title>
      <link>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/ux/design-research-on-laundry-habits/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2023 03:09:37 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/ux/design-research-on-laundry-habits/</guid>
      <description>Hunt Statement Background and initial Hunt statement In this research, we focus on the process of washing clothes and study the impact of clothes washing on the environment. A scoping tool: The 5Ws and 1H (Who, What, When, Where, Why, and How) is used to investigate a certain brief or context.
Pet owners were intrigued and decided to study. I myself am a pet owner, and there are many pet owners across the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ONEARTH — Energy Saving APP for GenGame</title>
      <link>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/ux/onearth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 03:12:54 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/ux/onearth/</guid>
      <description>THE BRIEF WHY CLIMATE CHANGE? Climate change happens because large amounts of greenhouse gases are released into the atmosphere as a result of many human activities worldwide, including, most importantly, burning fossil fuels for electricity generation, heating and transport. Climate change can alter our energy generation potential and energy needs.
WHY IT MATTERS? The impacts of climate change are increasing in frequency. People are at risk of overheating in their homes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design Inspiration: The Best Projects From December</title>
      <link>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/blog/design-inspiration-the-best-projects-from-december/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 13:45:06 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/blog/design-inspiration-the-best-projects-from-december/</guid>
      <description>Black Lines brand identity, by &amp;amp; Smith Black Lines wants it to be as easy to serve a Negroni as it is a pint of lager. The drinks company is seeking to revolutionise the bar experience by serving cocktails by draught with a changing menu of drinks (as well as same favourite stand-bys). A pink grapefruit spritz was served through the summer while a new pear and white tea fizz joins the line-up for winter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 10 Biggest Rebrands and Logo Designs of 2019</title>
      <link>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/blog/the-10-biggest-rebrands-and-logo-designs-of-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 13:40:00 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/blog/the-10-biggest-rebrands-and-logo-designs-of-2019/</guid>
      <description>Black Lines brand identity, by &amp;amp; Smith Black Lines wants it to be as easy to serve a Negroni as it is a pint of lager. The drinks company is seeking to revolutionise the bar experience by serving cocktails by draught with a changing menu of drinks (as well as same favourite stand-bys). A pink grapefruit spritz was served through the summer while a new pear and white tea fizz joins the line-up for winter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design Inspiration: The Best Projects From November</title>
      <link>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/blog/design-inspiration-the-best-projects-from-november/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 13:36:06 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/blog/design-inspiration-the-best-projects-from-november/</guid>
      <description>Black Lines brand identity, by &amp;amp; Smith Black Lines wants it to be as easy to serve a Negroni as it is a pint of lager. The drinks company is seeking to revolutionise the bar experience by serving cocktails by draught with a changing menu of drinks (as well as same favourite stand-bys). A pink grapefruit spritz was served through the summer while a new pear and white tea fizz joins the line-up for winter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pt Chooses Classic Blue for Its Colour of the Year 2020</title>
      <link>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/blog/pt-chooses-classic-blue-for-its-colour-of-the-year-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 13:32:54 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/blog/pt-chooses-classic-blue-for-its-colour-of-the-year-2020/</guid>
      <description>Black Lines brand identity, by &amp;amp; Smith Black Lines wants it to be as easy to serve a Negroni as it is a pint of lager. The drinks company is seeking to revolutionise the bar experience by serving cocktails by draught with a changing menu of drinks (as well as same favourite stand-bys). A pink grapefruit spritz was served through the summer while a new pear and white tea fizz joins the line-up for winter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 10 Biggest Product Stories of 2019</title>
      <link>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/blog/the-10-biggest-product-stories-of-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 12:58:17 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/blog/the-10-biggest-product-stories-of-2019/</guid>
      <description>Black Lines brand identity, by &amp;amp; Smith Black Lines wants it to be as easy to serve a Negroni as it is a pint of lager. The drinks company is seeking to revolutionise the bar experience by serving cocktails by draught with a changing menu of drinks (as well as same favourite stand-bys). A pink grapefruit spritz was served through the summer while a new pear and white tea fizz joins the line-up for winter.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
