<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>APP on Rosaline Xiao - Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/tags/app/</link>
    <description>Recent content in APP on Rosaline Xiao - Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 22:36:45 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rosalinexiao.github.io/tags/app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>DRT Bus Experience Design for Tourists</title>
      <link>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/ux/drt-bus-experience-design-for-tourists/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 22:36:45 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/ux/drt-bus-experience-design-for-tourists/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This project is a group work with three other students.
Team Leader: Xiangyu Xiao (me)：As the team leader, I am responsible for the overall project management, data analysis, determining the main features, prototype iteration, and video production.
Team members:
Jingkun Wei: Responsible for the user reseach Mengze Cai: Responsible for making the prototype, user evaluation and reflection Rhys Taylor: Responsible for the design book UN Goal background
The goal for this project is UN Goal No.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ONEARTH — Energy Saving APP for GenGame</title>
      <link>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/ux/onearth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 03:12:54 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/ux/onearth/</guid>
      <description>Energy Saving APP for GenGame ONEARTH is an smartphone app in partnership with GenGame energy. Based on a user-centered design approach, ONEARTH targets new parents who are short of money and time and encourages them to use smart meters to ensure the best living conditions for their family, allowing their baby to get the best start in life.
THE BRIEF WHY CLIMATE CHANGE? Climate change happens because large amounts of greenhouse gases are released into the atmosphere as a result of many human activities worldwide, including, most importantly, burning fossil fuels for electricity generation, heating and transport.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
