<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>APP on Rosaline Xiao - Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/tags/app/</link>
    <description>Recent content in APP on Rosaline Xiao - Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 22:36:45 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rosalinexiao.github.io/tags/app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>DRT Bus Experience Design for Tourists</title>
      <link>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/ux/drt-bus-experience-design-for-tourists/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 22:36:45 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/ux/drt-bus-experience-design-for-tourists/</guid>
      <description>Bus travel is efficient and sustainable yet restricts travellers to long fixed routes. Issues including difficulty locating bus stops, feelings of insecurity while waiting, and boredom contribute to tourists opting for unsustainable single-occupancy options like Uber.
However, according to the data from Transport &amp;amp; Environment, PHV drivers in England (including Uber drivers) produced over 81% of the total amount of CO2 in the UK. We aimed to create an innovative bus travel experience using VR and AR to improve enjoyment, flexibility, and convenience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ONEARTH — Energy Saving APP for GenGame</title>
      <link>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/ux/onearth/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 03:10:37 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/ux/onearth/</guid>
      <description>Energy Saving APP for GenGame ONEARTH is an smartphone app in partnership with GenGame energy. Based on a user-centered design approach, ONEARTH targets new parents who are short of money and time and encourages them to use smart meters to ensure the best living conditions for their family, allowing their baby to get the best start in life.
THE BRIEF WHY CLIMATE CHANGE? Climate change happens because large amounts of greenhouse gases are released into the atmosphere as a result of many human activities worldwide, including, most importantly, burning fossil fuels for electricity generation, heating and transport.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
