<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Creating &lt;span&gt;experiences&lt;/span&gt; that care about &lt;span&gt;user needs&lt;/span&gt; and &lt;span&gt;sustainability&lt;/span&gt; on Rosaline Xiao - Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/ux/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Creating &lt;span&gt;experiences&lt;/span&gt; that care about &lt;span&gt;user needs&lt;/span&gt; and &lt;span&gt;sustainability&lt;/span&gt; on Rosaline Xiao - Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 16:48:28 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/ux/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>PLANT COMPANION</title>
      <link>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/ux/plantcompanion/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 20:56:42 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/ux/plantcompanion/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In 2021, there were approximately 973 thousand males and 561 thousand females aged 16 to 44 living alone in the United Kingdom[1]. They crave love and emotional support. As a way to solve the loneliness problem, many young people living alone are eager to keep pets to accompany them, but they cannot due to various reasons. Many of them then choose to keep plants and regard plants as living companions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DRT Bus Experience Design for Tourists</title>
      <link>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/ux/drt-bus-experience-design-for-tourists/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 22:36:45 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/ux/drt-bus-experience-design-for-tourists/</guid>
      <description>Bus travel is efficient and sustainable yet restricts travellers to long fixed routes. Issues including difficulty locating bus stops, feelings of insecurity while waiting, and boredom contribute to tourists opting for unsustainable single-occupancy options like Uber.
However, according to the data from Transport &amp;amp; Environment, PHV drivers in England (including Uber drivers) produced over 81% of the total amount of CO2 in the UK. We aimed to create an innovative bus travel experience using VR and AR to improve enjoyment, flexibility, and convenience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eco Circle - An APP that increases recycling rates for Uni-campuses in collaboration with TPXimpact</title>
      <link>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/ux/industryproject/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 22:35:45 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/ux/industryproject/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This project is a group work with three other students.
The project is conducted in collaboration with TPXimpact, a digital transformation company based in the UK, supporting organisations to build a better future for people, places and the planet.
Team Members: Xiangyu Xiao (me), Mingjin Yang, Wen Zhou, Yifan Shi
Within the group, we generally use the Scrum Framework to arrange our project, because Scrum is an agile development methodology, which can double the development efficiency of the team and maximize the role of the team compared to the development method under the waterfall process; It can shorten the development cycle and improve the efficiency of project delivery(Leaders and Sennett, 2022).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ONEARTH — Energy Saving APP for GenGame</title>
      <link>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/ux/onearth/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 03:10:37 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/ux/onearth/</guid>
      <description>Energy Saving APP for GenGame ONEARTH is an smartphone app in partnership with GenGame energy. Based on a user-centered design approach, ONEARTH targets new parents who are short of money and time and encourages them to use smart meters to ensure the best living conditions for their family, allowing their baby to get the best start in life.
THE BRIEF WHY CLIMATE CHANGE? Climate change happens because large amounts of greenhouse gases are released into the atmosphere as a result of many human activities worldwide, including, most importantly, burning fossil fuels for electricity generation, heating and transport.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design Research on Laundry Habits in Loughborough</title>
      <link>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/ux/design-research-on-laundry-habits/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 03:09:37 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/ux/design-research-on-laundry-habits/</guid>
      <description>Hunt Statement Background and initial Hunt statement In this research, we focus on the process of washing clothes and study the impact of clothes washing on the environment. A scoping tool: The 5Ws and 1H (Who, What, When, Where, Why, and How) is used to investigate a certain brief or context.
Pet owners were intrigued and decided to study. I myself am a pet owner, and there are many pet owners across the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>S-Scooter - A sustainable way to travel in the 15-minute neighborhood in Loughborough</title>
      <link>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/ux/ford/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 03:12:52 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/ux/ford/</guid>
      <description>THE PROBLEM BEING TACKLED Brief “We are going to research the transportation methods and habits of the students living around Leicestershire, UK. So that design a sustainable way to optimize their traveling in the 15-minute neighborhood.”
As students at Loughborough University, we have found that many students lack a suitable means of transport when traveling between school and town, or to the library for study.
So to solve this problem, our idea was based on the conception of an immediate, free public transport option for short distances to meet the flexible travel needs of the student population</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
