<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Creating &lt;span&gt;experiences&lt;/span&gt; that care about &lt;span&gt;user needs&lt;/span&gt; and &lt;span&gt;sustainability&lt;/span&gt; on Rosaline Xiao - Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/ux/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Creating &lt;span&gt;experiences&lt;/span&gt; that care about &lt;span&gt;user needs&lt;/span&gt; and &lt;span&gt;sustainability&lt;/span&gt; on Rosaline Xiao - Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 16:48:28 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/ux/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>PLANT COMPANION</title>
      <link>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/ux/plantcompanion/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 20:56:42 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/ux/plantcompanion/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In 2021, there were approximately 973 thousand males and 561 thousand females aged 16 to 44 living alone in the United Kingdom[1]. They crave love and emotional support. As a way to solve the loneliness problem, many young people living alone are eager to keep pets to accompany them, but they cannot due to various reasons. Many of them then choose to keep plants and regard plants as living companions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DRT Bus Experience Design for Tourists</title>
      <link>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/ux/drt-bus-experience-design-for-tourists/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 22:36:45 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/ux/drt-bus-experience-design-for-tourists/</guid>
      <description>Introduction UN Goal background
The goal for this project is UN Goal No.11
SUSTAINABLE CITIES AND COMMUNITIES
The goal target is:
By 2030, provide access to safe, affordable, accessible and sustainable transport systems for all, improving road safety, notably by expanding public transport.
To achieve these goals, we decided to improve the bus ride experience by designing with buses in public transport. We wanted to provide a more convenient ride for passengers, and we found that tourists, as a group unfamiliar with the local environment, prefer to travel by taxi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design Research on Laundry Habits in Loughborough</title>
      <link>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/ux/design-research-on-laundry-habits/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2023 03:09:37 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/ux/design-research-on-laundry-habits/</guid>
      <description>Hunt Statement Background and initial Hunt statement In this research, we focus on the process of washing clothes and study the impact of clothes washing on the environment. A scoping tool: The 5Ws and 1H (Who, What, When, Where, Why, and How) is used to investigate a certain brief or context.
Pet owners were intrigued and decided to study. I myself am a pet owner, and there are many pet owners across the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ONEARTH — Energy Saving APP for GenGame</title>
      <link>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/ux/onearth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 03:12:54 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/ux/onearth/</guid>
      <description>Energy Saving APP for GenGame ONEARTH is an smartphone app in partnership with GenGame energy. Based on a user-centered design approach, ONEARTH targets new parents who are short of money and time and encourages them to use smart meters to ensure the best living conditions for their family, allowing their baby to get the best start in life.
THE BRIEF WHY CLIMATE CHANGE? Climate change happens because large amounts of greenhouse gases are released into the atmosphere as a result of many human activities worldwide, including, most importantly, burning fossil fuels for electricity generation, heating and transport.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
