<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Interactive Design on Rosaline Xiao - Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/tags/interactive-design/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Interactive Design on Rosaline Xiao - Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 00:30:46 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rosalinexiao.github.io/tags/interactive-design/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>S-Scooter</title>
      <link>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/ux/ford/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 00:30:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/ux/ford/</guid>
      <description>THE PROBLEM BEING TACKLED Brief “We are going to research the transportation methods and habits of the students living around Leicestershire, UK. So that design a sustainable way to optimize their traveling in the 15-minute neighborhood.”
As students at Loughborough University, we have found that many students lack a suitable means of transport when traveling between school and town, or to the library for study.
So to solve this problem, our idea was based on the conception of an immediate, free public transport option for short distances to meet the flexible travel needs of the student population</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PLANT COMPANION</title>
      <link>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/ux/plantcompanion/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 20:56:42 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/ux/plantcompanion/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In 2021, there were approximately 973 thousand males and 561 thousand females aged 16 to 44 living alone in the United Kingdom[1]. They crave love and emotional support. As a way to solve the loneliness problem, many young people living alone are eager to keep pets to accompany them, but they cannot due to various reasons. Many of them then choose to keep plants and regard plants as living companions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DRT Bus Experience Design for Tourists</title>
      <link>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/ux/drt-bus-experience-design-for-tourists/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 22:36:45 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rosalinexiao.github.io/portfolio/ux/drt-bus-experience-design-for-tourists/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This project is a group work with three other students.
Team Leader: Xiangyu Xiao (me)：As the team leader, I am responsible for the overall project management, data analysis, determining the main features, prototype iteration, and video production.
Team members:
Jingkun Wei: Responsible for the user reseach Mengze Cai: Responsible for making the prototype, user evaluation and reflection Rhys Taylor: Responsible for the design book UN Goal background
The goal for this project is UN Goal No.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
